Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
Cold
Couldn't they put in a few
more vending machines?
They can't. There are only so many
workers who can come in here.
Huh?
Where are the first-years?
On errands.
Bonito flakes.
Will they be okay?
Salmon.
They're not three years old.
They can handle an errand run.
No, that's not what I mean.
It's today, right?
The day Kyoto's principal comes.
To go over the exchange event.
Tuna.
Satoru's fighting with the higher-ups
because they arranged for
the first-years to get dispatched
on that special-grade case, right?
And the principal of Kyoto is
one of those higher-ups, isn't he?
So if they run into each other...
The first-year they were
targeting, Itadori, is dead.
I doubt he has any plans to do
anything about the other two.
Besides, the old man from Kyoto
won't cause a scene in broad daylight.
Salmon.
An instructor might have
his position to worry about,
but that's not the case for the students.
Are you saying Mai is coming?
It's just a guess.
Students aren't necessary for a meeting.
But still...
They love harassing us, right?
Both Toudou and Mai.
What are you doing here, Zenin-senpai?
Oh, she's one, too?
They do seem similar. Are they sisters?
They're twins.
Don't call me that, Fushiguro-kun.
You make me sound the same as Maki.
Call me Mai.
So these are the pinch hitters
for Okkotsu and the third-years?
We came here with the principal
because we were worried about you.
Your classmate died, right?
Was that rough?
Or did you think nothing of it?
What are you trying to say?
It's okay.
Some things are hard to say out loud.
So I'll say it for you.
"Vessel" makes it sound nice,
but it just means he was a half-curse monster.
Having such a tainted,
inhuman being beside you
brazenly calling himself a jujutsu
sorcerer must have been revolting, right?
Aren't you feeling better
now that he's dead?
Mai, don't bring up such pointless topics.
I'm only here to see if these guys
are fit to take Okkotsu's place.
That's all I want to know.
Fushiguro, was it?
What kind of woman is your type?
Depending on your answer,
I'll beat you half to death right here
and drag Okkotsu, or at least the
third-years, out to the exchange event.
By the way, my type is a
tall woman with a big ass!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 8:  Boredom
Why do I have to talk about
my taste in women with a guy I just met?
He's right. That's a tall hurdle
for an antisocial guy.
You be quiet.
This is confusing enough already.
You'll just make it more complicated.
Kyoto, third-year, Toudou Aoi.
Introduction over.
Now we're friends.
Hurry up and answer.
If you prefer men, that's fine, too.
A person's fetishes reflect
everything about them.
People with boring taste in women
are boring people themselves.
And I hate boring men.
The exchange event is where my soul can
be free as blood boils and flesh clashes.
Who knows what I might do if my
last exchange event ends up boring me?
Hey, aren't the Jujutsu Tech
schools four-year schools?
Only third-years and under
can join the exchange event.
Huh...
As a show of kindness, I'll let you
off only half-dead right now.
Answer me, Fushiguro.
What kind of woman is your type?
Is this some kind of comedy routine?
Is that your summer uniform?
Ticks me off, but it's nice.
Kugisaki's unarmed.
I'd rather avoid confrontation.
Not forgiving people isn't a bad thing.
That's just part of your kindness, isn't it?
I don't have a particular preference.
As long as she has unshakable
character, I won't ask for more.
Not a bad answer.
If you had said something like
"big boobs," I'd have killed you.
Shut up.
I knew it.
You're boring, Fushiguro.
Fushiguro!
Poor Fushiguro-kun.
Even a talented
second-grade jujutsu sorcerer
is nothing more than a first-year
against the top-grade Toudou-senpai.
I'll have to comfort him later.
I thought you two were similar,
but that's not the case at all.
Maki-san's a hundred times prettier.
Are you not sleeping enough?
You've got open pores.
I'll teach you...
how to speak to others.
I knew at first glance
that you were a boring guy.
But you shouldn't judge a
person by their looks, right?
So I went out of my way to ask you,
but you just trampled on my kindness.
Is your brain as pineapple as your head?
Toudou... That Toudou?
The one involved in last year's
unprecedented jujutsu terror attack
caused by the curse user, Getou—
Kabuki-cho First Street
The Night Parade of a Hundred Demons
from Kyoto to Shinjuku.
The one who exorcised a special-grade and five first-grade cursed spirits
by himself when the parade appeared in Kyoto?
That Toudou?
Still, there are several first-grade
sorcerers capable of beating a special-grade.
What's shocking is...
I heard you don't use cursed techniques.
Huh? Oh, that rumor's false.
I used them against the special-grade.
He doesn't use them against first-grades?!
Is he a monster?!
That's a relief to hear.
Nue, plus Gama!
Bottomless Well.
I'm up against a hardcore
close-range fighter.
I'll keep my distance and restrain him.
He's fast!
That wasn't his full speed earlier?!
Flimsy and shallow...
Both your body
and your taste in women!
Damn it!
His power is insane!
I'm not finished yet!
You're always
so boring!
I barely feel any intention to fight.
I've been holding back, and you're so proud?
If you're going to insist like that...
then I'll show you.
Bring it!
Don't move.
What are you two doing?!
Whew, just barely safe.
Bonito flakes.
Okay, I guess that might actually be an out.
Long time no see, Panda.
Why can't you just wait
until the exchange event?
Go on home, or I'll start screaming, "No!"
You don't have to tell me to go home.
Where'd I put my jacket?
Looks like I won't be bored the whole time.
Give Okkotsu a message for me:
"You take part, too."
What a pain.
I panda. I no understand human speech.
Salmon.
If you want to continue as a jujutsu sorcerer,
learn to choose who you pick a fight with.
What are you doing to our errand runner, Mai?
Oh, my. You're such a loser,
I didn't even notice you, Maki.
We're both equally losers, you know.
All you can do is imbue objects
with cursed energy,
and you've got shit for cursed techniques.
Better than having no cursed energy at all.
My neck gets sore looking up
at others all the time,
so I need to look down on someone
like you every so often.
Ah, forget it. We're both at
rock bottom, and it's pathetic.
Nobara, can you stand?
No way.
She won't be getting up for a while.
I hurt her pretty good...
What? You want to fight?
Nice support, Maki-san!
You put a bunch of holes
in my brand new tracksuit.
Leave that uniform of yours behind.
I'll make it my own summer uniform!
I'll put holes in your body next time.
Also, you wouldn't be able to wear
this with those long legs of yours—
Leave it!
We're leaving, Mai.
What?! No way...
Oh, there's my jacket.
Where's Fushiguro?
Don't worry. The others are with him.
Looks like you're having fun.
Quit joking! I'm just getting started!
No, you're not.
Unlike you, I still have
important business here in Tokyo.
My personal handshake with Takada-chan!
5 min
8th single "Youth Mineral" Release Celebration
Takada-chan
Tall Idol Takada-chan
Uh-huh...
Who knows what I might do if I miss my
transfer and can't make it to the event hall?
Come with me, Mai.
Ugh! You're so selfish!
Can't believe I lost the lottery
for the usual one in Kyoto.
Don't go thinking you'll get off
this easy at the exchange event.
Quit acting like you won!
Leave your uniform behind, damn it!
Cut it out, idiot.
Winning or losing here hardly matters.
We'll beat them up at the exchange event.
Hey, Maki-san...
Is what she said true?
That you don't have cursed energy?
It's true.
So I can't even see curses
without these glasses.
That's why I use cursed tools.
They already have curses imbued in them.
I can't pour my own cursed energy
into them to do things like you all do.
Like that thing he gave Itadori?
Then why are you a jujutsu sorcerer?
To spite them.
I can't wait to see the looks on my family's faces when I become a bigshot sorcerer,
after all the years they've
spent looking down on me.
Come on, let's hurry over to see Shouko-san.
I respect you, Maki-san.
That so?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Is Yaga here yet?
The time of an old man close
to death doesn't come cheap.
Principal Yaga won't be coming for a while.
Oh?
He was given a false schedule.
After some threats to Ijichi.
Thank you for the other day,
Principal Gakuganji.
Oh? What other day would that be?
Don't play dumb with me, old man.
I'm referring to the case with Itadori Yuuji.
As head of the conservatives,
you were involved too, correct?
My goodness, youth these days...
Don't you know how to be polite?
I never had any intention of respecting you.
Elders these days love to act important,
and it's so annoying, honestly.
Hey.
Your conduct is problematic.
I'll be reporting you to
the relevant authorities.
Oh, man!
It's Gojou Satoru in person!
Gojou Satoru in person!
Feel free.
I don't plan to chat for long.
He spoke! He spoke to me!
Last night, I was attacked by two
unregistered special-grade cursed spirits.
Oh? That is unfortunate.
Don't get me wrong here.
To me, it was about like being coerced
into taking a survey in the city.
So cool!
The two cursed spirits were
capable of communication,
and they probably have
allies who are just as strong.
It's not just our enemies, either.
Hakari, Okkotsu, and your Toudou...
The level of our students has risen
drastically in recent years, as well.
Then there was last year's
incident with Getou Suguru...
And now, the appearance of Sukuna's vessel.
What are you trying to say?
You don't know?
The wave of power you guys
have been trying to hold back
with your pointless status and traditions
has grown bigger than you can handle
and is now descending upon us.
You won't be able to measure
the coming age with the
classification of "special-grade."
If you think I'm the only
one who'll be fighting back,
you're going to get hurt, old man.
I think you are getting a bit out of line.
Oh, scary!
Well, that's all I wanted to say.
I'll be going now.
Oh, Principal Yaga will be
coming in about two hours.
Later!
Two hours?!
Miwa, would you go buy me some tea?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
If I can catch up to him, I'll get
him to take a picture with me!
Takada-chan Personal Handshake Event
Give me a Taka-tan Beam, please!
Okay, here I go!
Tan, Taka-tan!
Time's up.
One Month Later
Log\h\h\h\h\h——\h\h\hSeptember 2018
Kanagawa Prefecture, Kawasaki City
Kinema Cinema
Ticket Sales
Now Showing
Playing
After the showing,
three high school boys'
disfigured corpses were discovered by staff
Cause of death: increased cranial pressure and
respiratory paralysis due to cranial deformity
Excuse me...
Did you do that?
In the theater?
Wow. You can see me?
It's a gruesome sight.
Are you ready to witness it, Itadori-kun?
Thank you so much!
You're welcome.
I got a photo!
My tea?
Ah!
Juju Stroll
Personal Handshake Event
Event Hall
Hey, that hot lady is looking
at us like we're garbage!
Don't get turned on.
Mai, sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
Did something unpleasant happen?
Why don't you ask yourself that?
So this moment has finally come...
Huh?
5 min
8th single "Youth Mineral" Release Celebration
Takada-chan
What's this?
For the next handshake event.
You should go experience how
wonderful Takada-chan is in person.
It's just plain annoying.
This is my duty as a fan...
As a future husband.
That's just plain creepy.
But if I reject his offer,
he'll get even more annoying.
What's the matter?
Yeah, sure.
Huh?!
Wow, a girl!
It's your first time, right?
Yeah.
What's your name?
Mai.
Mai-chan, are you tired?
Did you wait long?
It was more the people than the line...
Then come back again
when you're feeling better.
I'll remember you, Mai-chan.
You're back, Mai?
How was it?
Fine.
True, Takada-chan isn't a woman
that can so easily be put into words.
She's not bad...
Episode 9:
Small Fry and Reverse Retribution
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org